<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Assigning Permission Sets</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/allocating-permission-sets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/allocating-permission-sets/</guid>
        <description>Setup Permission Sets You can assign 3 different types of permission sets to users. Each grants the user a different level of access to the app:
CON365, Setup - Enables the user to make changes to the Connector 365 Setup. CON365, Edit - Enables the user to further setup the app. For example managing email attachments, email subjects and similar. CON365, View - ENables the user to simply use the app.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Connector 365 Einrichtung</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/connector365-setup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/connector365-setup/</guid>
        <description>Setup Base App in the Connector 365 Setup You can use the search function of Business Central to access the Connector 365 setup:
There you will find two switches to set up the Base App:
The switch &amp;ldquo;Save Files in Joblist&amp;rdquo; determines whether documents created with the Connector 365 are saved in the activity list of the Connector 365. If the switch is activated, the reports are stored as files in the Business Central database and can be accessed via the activity list.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Reduction of Memory Usage</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/delete-activity-files/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/base/first-steps/setup/delete-activity-files/</guid>
        <description>Delete action for archived files Saving the report files in the activity list initially comes with the disadvantage of constantly increasing memory usage of the Business Central database. To counteract this, as of version 2.4.0.0 of the Base app, the Actions menu can be seen in the Connector 365 setup.
When the menu is opened, the function &amp;ldquo;Delete Activity Files&amp;rdquo; is showing.
After triggering the function, an input window appears where the start date (older date) for the delete action can be selected:</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>