<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Report default attachments</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-report/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-report/</guid>
        <description>Setup Adding default attachments per report Default attachments are a great way to save time when adding files to your emails. If you use the same attachment in every email, just add it as a default and it will be automatically attached to every email.
Start by opening the report selection of the report you want, in this example we will use Sales and Invoices. If you are not sure where to find the report selector, you can always use the Dynamics 365 Business Central search feature.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Customer default attachments</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-customer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-customer/</guid>
        <description>Setup Standard attachments per customer and report. Another way to add attachments is to add them as defaults for customers, for example, if there are conditions that only apply to a specific customer. Open the customer you want to add defaults to and expand the options in the menu via &amp;ldquo;More options&amp;rdquo;, click &amp;ldquo;Navigate&amp;rdquo; and select &amp;ldquo;Document layouts&amp;rdquo;.
If preferences have already been set in the report selection, it is possible to automatically attach them when setting up attachments per customer - simply click the &amp;ldquo;Copy from Report Selection&amp;rdquo;.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Document default attachments</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-document/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/defaults-document/</guid>
        <description>Setup The following describes how to add document attachments, i.e. the document attachments from a specific document as an attachment, or how to add document line attachments, i.e. the document attachments from the document lines.
Add Document Attachments per Document Using the fact box, each document can have document attachments that are automatically attached when the document is sent. To do this, select the desired document in the overview and select &amp;ldquo;Attachments&amp;rdquo; in the fact box on the right.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Special features when using Connector 365 XRechnung</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/xrechnung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/mail-attachments-plus/first-steps/setup/xrechnung/</guid>
        <description>Special features when using Connector 365 XRechnung If you have installed the Connector 365 XInvoice app, an additional field is available when adding attachments,
which directly affects the way the Connector 365 XInvoice app works.
This is because the latter is compatible with the Connector 365 Mail Attachments Plus app. This means that attachments set up for customers, reports or receipts are also taken into account when sending XRechnung using the Connector 365 XInvoice app.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>