<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Using the Connector 365 Upgrade App on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Using the Connector 365 Upgrade App on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Upgrade of joblist(CON Joblist)</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/joblist_transfer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/joblist_transfer/</guid>
        <description>Upgrade from Connector 365 setup Please check the prerequisites before proceeding.
The Joblist logs all activities performed as part of the Connector NAV/BC functions.
The Connector 365 Apps use a similar table (Connector 365 Activities) to record any activities.
However, as the two tables are not identical, a process is required to transfer the data from the Joblist to the Connector 365 Activities list.
The Connector 365 Upgrade app provides a function for data synchronisation.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Upgrade of communication matrix (CON Communication Matrix)</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/matrix_transfer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/connector-upgrade/using-the-upgrade-app/matrix_transfer/</guid>
        <description>Upgrade of communication matrix (CON Communication Matrix) Introduction Please check the prerequisites before proceeding.
<<<<<<< HEAD
The communication matrix of the Connector NAV/BC contains, if maintained, setup data that determines if and how documents for individual customers, vendors or contacts are processed. In the product series Connector 365 (Business Central versions &amp;gt; 14), the communication matrix is no longer available as a separate table.
=======
The communication matrix of the Connector NAV/BC contains, if maintained, setup data that determines if and how documents for individual customers, vendors or contacts are processed.
In the product series Connector 365 (Business Central versions &amp;gt; 14), the communication matrix is no longer available as a separate table.
>>>>>>> a0b69aea4c6f75cb1d52988de0675995ff634de6
Instead, the Document Layouts are used for similar facilities.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>