<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brief description / overview on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brief description / overview on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Core functionalities</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/kernfunktionalitaeten/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/kernfunktionalitaeten/</guid>
        <description>Core functionalities The core functionalities can be summarized as follows:
Complete integration in Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central (from NAV 4.x) Flexible evaluation of &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo; facts from the enterprise resource planning area Evaluation of freely definable &amp;ldquo;soft&amp;rdquo; criteria Free weighting of all criteria and criteria groups Definition and delimitation of different supplier groups Delimitation of the articles to be evaluated from category to variant Determination and evaluation of a complaint rate by integration of the complaint module Inclusion of qualitative, quantitative and other product characteristics, which can be determined at the</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Weighting</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/gewichtung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/gewichtung/</guid>
        <description>Weighting The weighting of the selected factors for classification is carried out via two weighting levels: First, the individual defined criteria are subjected to weighting, and second, the criteria groups (hard/soft) are weighted against each other. In
In total, 100 % are assigned in each case (cf. Figure 1).
Figure 1: Methods for supplier evaluation.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Criteria</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/kriterien/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/kriterien/</guid>
        <description>Criteria The selection of the relevant evaluation criteria of an object is summarized in a criteria pool.
summarized. Such objects can be, for example, suppliers, supplier groups,
articles, article categories etc. The scope of this selection is set up at the evaluation itself. After selecting the criterion, it is defined whether the criterion is soft
or hard. Hard&amp;quot; criteria are automatically determined and included from the merchandise management
and included. &amp;ldquo;Soft&amp;rdquo; criteria, on the other hand, are freely defined and assigned values.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Selection of the evaluation</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/auswahl-der-auswertung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/auswahl-der-auswertung/</guid>
        <description>Selection of the evaluation After the definition of the criteria, the evaluation can be defined individually for each criterion.
can be defined individually for each criterion. For this purpose, all fields from the tables &amp;ldquo;Purchasing line&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Purchasing delivery line&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Purchasing line archive&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Quality log&amp;rdquo; are available for selection. You can also
compare newly added fields in the named tables. How you relate the fields to each other
to each other is freely definable and is represented by a formula.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Awarding of points</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/punktevergabe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/punktevergabe/</guid>
        <description>Awarding of points Points are awarded for each evaluation. For this purpose, a value range and its total number of points must be specified or set up.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Keying</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/schluesselung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/schluesselung/</guid>
        <description>Keying The &amp;ldquo;soft&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo; evaluation criteria deposited at the evaluation are weighted. The way in which the soft and hard criteria are incorporated into the overall evaluation is stored at the evaluation (cf. Figure 1).</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Evaluation prerequisites</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/bewertungsvorraussetzungen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/bewertungsvorraussetzungen/</guid>
        <description>Evaluation prerequisites Optionally, the evaluation prerequisite for the sales minimum,
the purchase order item minimum, the delivery item minimum and the archive item minimum. This means, for example, that suppliers with a certain minimum
minimum sales can be taken into account in the evaluation.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Classification</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/klassifizierung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/klassifizierung/</guid>
        <description>Classification Classification is carried out on the basis of the defined evaluation criteria and their weighting.
is carried out. In the process, the supplier achieves a number of points which defines his classification
(achieved class) is defined.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Evaluations</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/auswertung/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/auswertung/</guid>
        <description>Evaluation Three evaluations in the form of reports are available in stages to determine the results:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Setting up the ratings</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/einrichtung-der-bewertungen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/easy-supra/kurzbeschreibung/einrichtung-der-bewertungen/</guid>
        <description>Setting up the ratings Each rating can be conveniently set up via a 5-step wizard and changed afterwards.
change them afterwards. With the help of a setup wizard, the user is guided through all the necessary
necessary steps for a successful setup. The entries made are partially subjected to a plausibility check.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>