<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setup on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Basic setup</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/base-setup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/base-setup/</guid>
        <description>Basic setup To set up the basic settings for the Connector 365 XRechnung app, navigate via the search bar
to the Connector 365 setup.
The Connector 365 XRechnung app extends the setup page with a dedicated XInvoice section.
The XRechnung section contains the following fields and setting options:
Field Meaning Validate XRechnung Yes, if XRechnung files are to be validated using the XRechnung validator. No, to not validate XRechnung files. XRechnung version The currently used XRechnung version.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Buyer Reference / Leitweg-Id</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-ident-id/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-ident-id/</guid>
        <description>Buyer reference The buyer reference represents an identifier that uniquely identifies a customer.
The XRechnung standard uses the concept of the Leitweg-Id for addressing public sector customers.
You can read more about the Leitweg-Id below.
In principle, however, the XRechnung standard can also be used in the non-public sector.
Here, usually no Leitweg-Ids are used, but own identifiers.
Leitweg-Id The Leitweg-Id must be indicated on every electronic invoice sent to public-sector customers of the federal administration.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Customer</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-customer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-customer/</guid>
        <description>Setup Customer The customer-specific settings for sending XRechnung are made in the Document layouts of the respective customer.
When you open the document layouts, the following additional fields will be available after installing the Connector 365 XInvoice app:
Buyer Reference Add document as attachment In the field Buyer Reference the id of the customer is entered. This is necessary to uniquely identify an invoice recipient.
The customer reference can also be set in the e-mail dialog, i.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>VAT Scheme</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-vat-scheme/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-vat-scheme/</guid>
        <description>Setup Checking the VAT Scheme You should check the VAT scheme codes for the respective countries. For XRechnung, this is normally only Germany.
These can be changed under “Countries/Region“ in Business Central, the fastest way to find this point is via the search function.
There you change the field “VAT Scheme“ to the code for the corresponding country. The code for Germany is 9930, all other codes can be found here.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Unit codes</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-unit-codes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-unit-codes/</guid>
        <description>Setup Check standard codes for units Another point worth checking are unit codes. These must have a special designation to be PEPPOL compliant in order to be accepted.
The quickest way to get to the list of unit codes is to use the search function and search for “Units of Measure”.
Then you should adjust the field &amp;ldquo;International Standard Code” according to the UN/ECE Recommendation 20 or 21.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Tax Category</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-tax-category/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-tax-category/</guid>
        <description>Setup Check the Tax Category It is also worth looking at the tax category, which can be found in the VAT Posting Setup. This again can be called up most quickly via the search function.
Here you should now fill the field “Tax category” with the respective designation, you can find this here finden. In most cases you will only need E S and Z.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Seller Country Code</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-seller-country-code/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/setup-seller-country-code/</guid>
        <description>Setup Check the Seller Country Code One point that must also be taken into account is setting up the seller country code according to the ISO 3166 standard.
The code is set in the company data:
For more information on how to set up the code correctly, see the corresponding Wikipedia page.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Document Sending Profile</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/doc-sending-profile/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/xrechnung/first-steps/setup/doc-sending-profile/</guid>
        <description>Setup Document Sending Profile The document sending profile is a standard functionality of Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central.
It is used to control the preferred method of sending sales documents. By default, the functionality is intended for use with &amp;ldquo;Post and Send&amp;rdquo;. Connector 365 XRechnung extends this functionality by adding the option XRechnung to the possible profiles.
Set up document send profiles To set up a document sending profile
Open the search, type document sending profile and then select the appropriate link.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>