<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working with Custom Filename on Connector 365 Online Help</title>
    <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working with Custom Filename on Connector 365 Online Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year} - Germany - BELWARE® GmbH - Dorsten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Scenarios for Custom Filename</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/scenarios/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/scenarios/</guid>
        <description>Scenarios for using Connector 364 Custom Filename. Resolving custom filenames including wildcards currently works for the following tasks:
Send standard email Attach document as PDF Connector 364 Easy Batch Send document to data medium (PDF or electronic document) Connector 364 XInvoice Connector 364 E-Post </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Send by E-Mail</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/maildialogue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/maildialogue/</guid>
        <description>Send by e-mail File name in mail dialog After setting up for file names, you are now ready to actively use your previously defined file name(s).
Using your own file names for e-mail attachments First open one of the documents you have set up and then open the desired document (if applicable, that of a customer/vendor you have set up). Now click on &amp;ldquo;Print/Send &amp;ldquo; -&amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Send by e-mail &amp;ldquo;. The dialog for sending by mail will open.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Attach as PDF</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/attach-as-pdf/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/attach-as-pdf/</guid>
        <description>Attach as PDF Provided you have made the appropriate setup, the Connector 365 Custom Filename function is also available for the Append as PDF function.
Attach document as PDF In some document types, the Append as PDF function is available by default.
In the Posted Sales Invoices example, you can find it under the Print/Send action.
If you execute it, a PDF file will be created from the selected document, and attached to the same document.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Send...</title>
        <link>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/send/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://docs.belware.de/en-us/apps/custom-filename/working-with-custom-filename/send/</guid>
        <description>Send Via the action Send&amp;hellip; you have the possibility to combine different processing and sending methods.
By clicking the action Send&amp;hellip; a dialog window opens.
shipping/processing type Printer Yes (prompt for settings) Yes (Use default settings) Email Yes (Prompt for settings) Yes (Use default settings) data carrier PDF Electronic Receipt PDF and electronic receipt XInvoice Yes (Prompt for settings) Yes (Use default settings) Electronic receipt Yes (Prompt for settings) Yes (Use default settings) E-mail Yes (Prompt for settings) Yes (Use default settings) </description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>